<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <!-- Case Study 3: Marketplace-to-Retail Expansion -->
    <template id="snippet_wf_case_study_3" name="Warefor Case Study 3 - Retail Expansion">
        <!-- Hero Section -->
        <section class="wf-cs-hero">
            <img src="/warefor_website/static/src/img/case-retail-aisle.jpg" alt="Retail Store Aisle" class="wf-cs-hero-bg"/>
            <div class="wf-cs-hero-overlay"></div>
            <div class="container">
                <div class="wf-cs-hero-content">
                    <a href="/case-studies" class="wf-cs-back">
                        <i class="fa fa-arrow-left"></i> Back
                    </a>
                    <h1 class="wf-cs-title">Marketplace-to-Retail Expansion</h1>
                    <p class="wf-cs-subtitle">Scaling from Online Success to Nationwide Store Distribution</p>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>

        <!-- Content Section -->
        <section class="wf-cs-content">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row justify-content-center">
                    <div class="col-lg-8">
                        <!-- The Challenge -->
                        <div class="wf-cs-section">
                            <h2 class="wf-cs-section-title">The Challenge</h2>
                            <p>A fast-growing international cookware brand achieved strong success selling online through major U.S. marketplaces. However, expanding into brick-and-mortar retail presented a fundamentally different set of challenges.</p>
                            <p>Unlike e-commerce, selling through physical stores requires:</p>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-list">
                                <li>Rigid compliance with retailer-specific logistics and data standards</li>
                                <li>Store-ready packaging that protects the product while presenting well on the shelf</li>
                                <li>Flawless item setup, where minor errors can cascade into costly downstream issues</li>
                                <li>Deep understanding of legacy retail systems and processes unfamiliar to many manufacturers operating abroad</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p>When a leading U.S. big-box retailer invited the brand to begin selling in stores, the brand was referred to Warefor to support the transition.</p>
                        </div>

                        <!-- The Solution -->
                        <div class="wf-cs-section">
                            <h2 class="wf-cs-section-title">The Solution</h2>
                            <p>Warefor partnered with the brand to design and execute a retail-ready distribution operation, drawing on decades of experience supporting major U.S. retailers.</p>
                            
                            <h3 class="wf-cs-subsection-title">Retail Readiness &amp; Execution</h3>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-list">
                                <li>Advising on store-ready packaging that withstands the logistics environment while maintaining strong in-store presentation</li>
                                <li>Managing complex item setup and retail master data, reducing risk of chargebacks and operational friction</li>
                                <li>Applying disciplined receiving, storage, and outbound processes to minimize damage, claims, and losses</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h3 class="wf-cs-subsection-title">Systems, EDI &amp; Visibility</h3>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-list">
                                <li>Implementing reliable workflows around electronic data interchange (EDI)—an older but mission-critical retail technology unfamiliar to many international manufacturers</li>
                                <li>Providing full remote visibility through Warefor's platform, allowing the brand to monitor inventory levels, inbound and outbound activity, and product movement in real time</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h3 class="wf-cs-subsection-title">Sales &amp; Inventory Support</h3>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-list">
                                <li>Supporting inventory planning and forecasting at the store and network level</li>
                                <li>Aligning inbound flows with expected sell-through to support expansion while protecting service levels</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>

                        <!-- The Results -->
                        <div class="wf-cs-section">
                            <h2 class="wf-cs-section-title">The Results</h2>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-list">
                                <li>Rapid retail expansion driven by consistent execution and strong online, in-full performance</li>
                                <li>Store count growth across multiple national retailers</li>
                                <li>Warefor directly handled, stored, and shipped every unit placed in more than 5,000 retail stores across the United States</li>
                                <li>In-store performance mirrored the brand's prior online success, enabling continued growth with additional retail partners</li>
                            </ul>
                        </div>

                        <!-- Why It Matters Callout -->
                        <div class="wf-cs-callout">
                            <h3 class="wf-cs-callout-title">Why It Matters</h3>
                            <p>This engagement demonstrates Warefor's ability to:</p>
                            <ul class="wf-cs-callout-list">
                                <li>Bridge the gap between marketplace fulfillment and physical retail distribution</li>
                                <li>Reduce risk for international brands entering complex U.S. retail channels</li>
                                <li>Combine operational excellence, systems expertise, and sales support into a single execution model</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p class="wf-cs-callout-cta"><strong>Strong products win online. Disciplined execution wins on the shelf. Warefor delivers both.</strong></p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>
</odoo>
